I am sky from Friday Night Funkin' Sky
I'm the Reborn version of the 2021 mod, Vs Sky
I'm the new Sky, the 2025 version
Anyone says I'm bad is just stupid as fuck
I have cutouts of my Boyfriend all over the place
Because I kiss on them all day, and I won't stop it
I want him for myself, only want him for myself
I just can't stop thinking about him all day
I just wanna take him to my bedroom and #$!? him so bad
And he will be satisfied as heck
And I know it, definitely
I wanna date him so damn badly
I wanna take him to my bed
So I can do a lot of
I just want him to love me and I'll love him back
I'll do anything he asks, and I won't hesitate
All I want is love
Is that too, much to ask
From you?
I just want you to love me
And stop dating that
Whore
You
Call
Girlfriend
You don't need her
You need me
Not some fucking bitch
That
Pretends to love you like that
Bet she doesn't need you
You need me
Hi I'm Sky: REBORN but I am a yandere
I now have a knife
And I'll stab you to death
I'm gonna stab you and pull all your damn guts out
And sell them on wish.com for a very high price
All I want is you.